{
    "subject": "resource/Ibarreta",
    "predicate": "property/subdivisionType",
    "object": "Country",
    "human_readable": "Ibarreta is a country.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9862987399101257,
            "question": "Is Ibarreta a country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7326135039329529,
            "question": "Where is Ibarreta located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4434753656387329,
            "question": "Does Ibarreta have a rich cultural heritage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4278292953968048,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist destinations in Ibarreta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4227612614631653,
            "question": "What is the capital of Ibarreta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37311920523643494,
            "question": "Who is the current leader of Ibarreta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3092082440853119,
            "question": "What are some major industries in Ibarreta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2960546612739563,
            "question": "What is the currency used in Ibarreta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2958041727542877,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Ibarreta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27318400144577026,
            "question": "What language is spoken in Ibarreta?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ibarreta is a country.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1888_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Ibarreta?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1888_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the currency used in Ibarreta?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1888_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some major industries in Ibarreta?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1888_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1888_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1888_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1888_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1888_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1888_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1888_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1888_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1888_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1888_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1888_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe documents provided contain information about the city of Ibarreta, its location, and details about the surname Ibarreta. However, none of this information suggests that Ibarreta is a country. It is mentioned as a city in Formosa, Argentina. Therefore, the triple \"Ibarreta is a country\" is not supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents clearly indicate that Ibarreta is a city or town located in the Formosa province of Argentina. There is no information suggesting that it is a country."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}